http://www.bernardresnick.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy |
Bernard M. Resnick, Esq., P.C.
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to Bernard M. Resnick, Esq., P.C. (“we” or “us”). This privacy policy is intended both to: 1) describe how our website may collect and use information from your Internet enabled device (i.e., your computer, tablet, smartphone or other device, and browsers or apps used to access the Internet), and 2) describe how you may opt out of any such collection and use. Please contact us if you have questions about our privacy policy.
Data collection and cookies. Features or partners of our website may collect data including, but not limited to: the number of visitors to our site, the time spent on our site and pages clicked, the types of devices used to access our site, and the Internet Protocol (IP) addresses of visitors. We use this information to improve our website and marketing. This data is collected by sending cookies (or similar tracking technology) to your device. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology; if you previously provided personally identifiable information, however, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties; and this privacy policy does not cover third parties’ use of cookies. You may configure your device to limit or prevent access by cookies, such as to notify you when you receive a cookie, to block all cookies, or to delete existing cookies.
Partners and features that collect information. Our website marketing partners or features that collect data as described above may include, among others, Google Analytics and other analytics programs.
Use these links to learn how Google uses data it collects, to prevent Google Analytics from using data from your device, or to opt out of Google’s interest-based ads.
Information you send us. Please see our disclaimer, which generally addresses information you intentionally send us using e-mail or any contact form on this website. If you submit your name or contact information to us, we may use it to send you information about our services. You may opt out of receiving further information from us by contacting us or, where applicable, by using an “unsubscribe” option included in our communications. We will not sell or give your personally identifying information to other parties for their own direct advertising purposes.
Changes to this policy. We reserve the right to update this policy. If we make updates, we will change the modification date below.
Last modified: 2/22/19.
Two Bala Plaza - Suite 300 • Bala Cynwyd, PA 19004 • Voice: (610) 660-7774
©
Bernard M. Resnick, Esq., P.C. All Rights Reserved. Privacy Policy
